If he says 'Yuck' then give him a slap
Dada Dada Dada
Kaluda or else
aunt or cameraman brother brother with cameraman brother with cameraman mother with cameraman
too if the cameraman has
not changed then the
slap has definitely changed stone Remi
Dada's beatings are agonizingly painful
listen my mother is also the cameraman with cameraman
with
cameraman what does he like
cola
you also like cola
[music] I had
n't heard that
Kalu's beating is agonizingly painful if sin is agonizing then sin is agonizingly painful [
bell sound]
[music]
this
my uncle and brother
baba
you should at
least
forget your
faith for a day then you should be happy then you should be happy
happiness
namaskar happy stay
ka saala aye [screaming sound] ka
[music]
Guru
Nani [music]
yes whatever
shooting is going on yes whatever shooting is going on
slowly have you seen kole kole
listen seta seta
to
[music] say I
love you
O say set to say I love you too
Actually people are
crazy crazy
[laughs]
no race Guruji let's go there let's
go
[music]
but complete  You will ruin me, you wo
n't live, if you
hit gold then hello hello, otherwise it's not
okay
shooting guru
[music]
Ayushmann
[laughs] [music
] let
me see, see
[laughs]
oh god your leela
[laughs] then it's
okay
[laughs]
oh baap
oh kundali
[laughs]
no,
come on Nikhilta
maal ke bya bolsi, look
away you bastard koliy,
you are a very rascal, the one for
marriage
hello
yes priest namaskar yes yes Ayushmann
Ayushmann
yes chowkiani
[sound of clearing throat]
[nasal sound]
party wala mil yes
awesome
puja pujai complete, complete, dazzling, complete oh don't
worry about the
expenses
oh look, do the complete puja 25000 expense
puja accident wala
you have four cars
[laughs]
four cars,
cars, four pedestals, second hand, the pedestal, the pedestal, the pedestal, the pedestal, the pedestal
[laughs]
look we poor people have four pedestals,
you do the puja
Call it a cart, don't do puja, cart, vomit,
yes, listen, don't take any expenses, do puja, it hurts,
this is not what you have done, take online
photos, do online puja, online payment,
Baba
Baba [laughter] Baba
Baba Johar Baba,
Ayushman, the [ __ ] is
not satisfied at all, get up, get up [
laughter] get up, get up here [
laughter]
you go to the doctor, go, go, go,
Nikhil, Nikhil, I am the Guru, I want a doctor,
Baba, give me Guru, give me
[sound of clearing throat] Baba, give me Guru
[music] get the
operation done, go,
go, raise your hands,
Baba, you [ __ ] me for 350, Guru, [ __ ] me, Baba, take
500,
okay, set the ticket
[music]
Baba, the whole hair is all jhan
[laughter]
Baba, [ __ ] me hard, [ __ ] me hard
[screaming sound]
[music]
even the Guru
doesn't have the
goods for the kirtan program
[laughter]
but pink color is
dangerous,
start quickly,
Guru,
that's the whole
thing
[music]
Gulab Pholo Gulab Pholo
Aao Gute Gulab Pholo [song voice]
aa de go aa de re
bolo [song voice]
re bolo aa
de  [Song voice] Go aa deha
re bolo
[laughter]
This is a flower flower flower e open open
flower flower [music] Flower e open open
flower flower so it's okay
hey people rose flower ke
gulaabila
[laughter] start start koke
moragi jaisi mor Radha Radha phule mor Radha Radha phule raag raage mo dekhi hasi desi mor
Radha Radha
phule aisi
mo Radha [Song voice] Radhasi
gulgul sul supti
mo Radha [Song voice] Radha aisi o Radha
Radha
[music]
Guru bahut salu hindi ke hindi
I'm so crazy about
that thing
ji
[laughter]
I'm so crazy about that thing [music] I'm so crazy about that
thing
[music]
Hero hi lala I'm hero Hirala Hero hi la
Hero hi la Hero hila I'm hero Hirala Hero
[music] Hila I'm hero
hi
la
Guru bhi
babu
look look jali
nila look look maar kha
favourite
oe maarle
Favourite Song
[Music]
Guruma
Learn kirtan from the program,
you do
multiple big
work, I will marry you, I will run away, I will give you
home, I will give you home tomorrow too
[Laughter]
Yes, you reach home empty handed today only
[Laughter] I will give you ragi to
drink, I will
not go
[Music] If you
want to see it, you should see it, I will not see it,
brother, I will give you a drink, will I not
see it, no, no, no, let's go, I will pull it
[Music] If you want to get
married, then
definitely get the peacock outside [Laughter] I
heard this voice, hello hello dhan hello hello dhan hello dhan aye
hello keep it one day,
otherwise two days five gears, don't come quickly
[Music] [Music] [Music]
[Music]
Boss, take it easy, Johar, I will not say anything, I will not go home
Babu,
mother, I will come home,
son, I will come very soon,
how many more days will it take,
two days, it will take the day, I will not
touch it, but do
n't go home,
son, two more days,
two-three days are left, mother, whatever you want to
check,
Babu
[nasal voice]
Hello, no, no,
you are not a bastard, oh
God, you are
just a robber
[music] you
break my body, hey, what have
you done, I have no respect, I have no good, I have
said a penny medicine [music] don't forget, forgive me, I have forgiven you, I have no other
house, the cameraman also has a house, so I have to take care of him,
mother, mother, guru, two months, I have touched him, I have to give him the
cricket team, hey
brother, come on, what's the big deal
[laughs]
this,
then the
people of the [ __ ] are ruining my life, ruining my life,
ruining my life, friend, stop me, tell me, I am
helpless, why is it helpless, should
I go to the police station, you worry about it,
listen
[music]
brother, what do you
say, brother, I do
n't have the vermilion,
God, don't give it even to the enemy, hey, may my father-in-law be blessed with
marriages,
know that
even my father-in-law has touched me by playing, he has
not cried at home
[music] [
music] the
result of my sins in life,
yes, if it is cancer, please cure it, God, cure the money of the poor
people, cure the money of the poor people  I am
very sad, I am
not
happy, Aman
[Music]
listen, you support me, support me,
oh, cancer is fine,
you support me, without any reason,
my mother is a cancer patient, the rest I will
not kill you by touching, if I can cure you by touching, if I can cure sister-in-law's
mother, then
please what, I will not
tell you,
but my profit, profit,
profit, 50, it is
not right,
but you will waste all the
money,
see the land, I remember, you are not wasting money, life is my life
[Music] but money, life, I am
giving you a lot of pain to the enemy [Music] I am
helpless, I have a
lot of money, the rest is my life [Music] I will
not give you any money, I will save you
[Music] I can
earn a living by donating, donate it to a cancer patient
[Music] a
lot of life, a lot of
daily expenses, but I can
donate my life, today life is not
available.